https://chiefsleuven.be/cookie-policy-eu/

Skip to content
Home
Covid Protocols
Info
Cookie policy (EU)
Tweedehands
This Cookie Policy was last updated on 25/04/2020 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.1. IntroductionOur website, https://chiefsleuven.be (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. Cookies5.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.5.2 Analytical cookiesBecause statistics are being tracked anonymously, no permission is asked to place analytical cookies.5.3 Advertising cookiesOn this website we use advertising cookies, enabling us to gain insights into the campaign results. This happens based on a profile we create based on your behavior on https://chiefsleuven.be. With these cookies you, as website visitor, are linked to a unique ID but these cookies will not profile your behavior and interests to serve personalized ads.5.4 Marketing/Tracking cookiesMarketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage, used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.Because these cookies are marked as tracking cookies, we ask your permission to place these.5.5 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter en Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter en Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter en Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter en Instagram are located in the United States.6. Placed cookiesCookie Notice for GDPR
Gebruik
We gebruiken Cookie Notice for GDPR voor cookie toestemming registratie. Lees meer
Delen van gegevens
Deze data wordt niet gedeeld met derde partijen.
Functioneel
Naam
cookie_notice_accepted
Retentie
permanent
Functie
Checkt of cookies kunnen worden geplaatst
Polylang
Gebruik
We gebruiken Polylang voor taal management. Lees meer
Delen van gegevens
Deze data wordt niet gedeeld met derde partijen.
Voorkeuren
Naam
pll_language
Retentie
permanent
Functie
Store language settings
Automattic
Gebruik
We gebruiken Automattic voor website ontwikkeling. Lees meer
Delen van gegevens
Voor meer informatie, lees de Automattic Privacyverklaring.
Statistieken
Naam
tk_ai
Retentie
sessie
Functie
Opslaan van een unieke gebruikers ID
0
Gebruik
We gebruiken Facebook voor het vertonen van recente posts en/of social share buttons. Lees meer
Delen van gegevens
Voor meer informatie, lees de Facebook Privacyverklaring.
Marketing/Tracking
Naam
actppresence
Retentie
1 jaar
Functie
Regelen van frequentie van weergegeven advertenties
Naam
Gebruik
We gebruiken Twitter voor het vertonen van recente posts en/of social share buttons. Lees meer
Delen van gegevens
Voor meer informatie, lees de Twitter Privacyverklaring.
Functioneel
Naam
local_storage_support_test
Retentie
permanent
Functie
Load balancing functionaliteiten
Marketing/Tracking
Delen van gegevens
Deze data wordt niet gedeeld met derde partijen.
0
Naam
wp-saving-post
Retentie
Functie
Diversen
Gebruik
Delen van gegevens
Functie
7. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on "Save preferences", you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.7.1 Manage your consent settings8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Chiefs Leuven
Ondernemingenweg 1, 3001 Leuven
Belgium
Website: https://chiefsleuven.be
Email: GDPR@chiefsleuven.be
Phone number: 0032 (0)16 40 30 60
Thuis wedstrijden
View all events
Facebook
